<?xml version="1.0"?>
<metadata>
	<idinfo>
		<citation>
			<citeinfo>
				<origin>Rocky Mountain National Park GIS Program</origin>
				<pubdate>19950101</pubdate>
				<title>Lakes of Rocky Mountain National Park</title>
				<geoform Sync="TRUE">vector digital data</geoform>
				<serinfo>
					<sername>none</sername>
					<issue>none</issue>
				</serinfo>
				<pubinfo>
					<pubplace>Estes Park, Colorado</pubplace>
					<publish>Rocky Mountain National Park GIS Program</publish>
				</pubinfo>
				<onlink>http://nrdata.nps.gov/romo/romodata/lakes.zip</onlink>
				<ftname Sync="TRUE">Lakes</ftname></citeinfo>
		</citation>
		<descript>
			<abstract>
These data depict the hydrography (water) resources of Rocky Mountain National Park.
It is derived and developed from a number of sources.  These include:

&gt; 1:24000-scale USGS Digital Line Graph (DLG) data,
&gt; 1:24000-scale USFS Cartographic Feature File (CFF) data,
&gt; GPS (Global Positioning System) data.

These data have also been updated and upgraded using heads-up digitizing using USGS DOQ's and color DOQ's developed for Rocky Mountain National Park as a backdrop.

**NOTE**  - These data are available as either an ESRI coverage, or as separate ESRI shapefiles, and this one metadata file is valid for all those data.  

When in COVERAGE format, both arc and polygon data are in the one dataset.  Due to the limitations of the ESRI shapefile format, this hydrography data is contained in two separate shapefiles: Lakes.shp (polygons) and Streams.shp (vectors).  

These data were originally compiled in 1995, and have been incrementally updated and upgraded as needed.

These data depict only vector and polygon features (streams, lakes, etc.).  Point hydrography features (wells, springs, diversions, etc.) are located in other datasets of the Rocky Mountain National Park GIS database.

These data cover a 39 quad area centered on Rocky Mountain National Park.  The 7.5 minute USGS quads covered are: 

Clark Peak, Chambers Lake, Comanche Peak, Pingree Park, Crystal Mountain, Mount Richthofen, Fall River Pass, Trail Ridge, Estes Park, Glen Haven, Bowen Mountain, Grand Lake, McHenrys Peak, Longs Peak, Panorama Peak, Trail Mountain, Shadow Mountain, Isolation Peak, Allens Park, Raymond, Granby, Strawberry Lake, Monarch Lake, Ward, Gold Hill, Rawah Lakes, Boston Peak, Kinikinik, Rustic, Big Narrows, Poudre Park, Buckhorn Mountain, Drake, Pinewood Lake, Lyons, Boulder, Laporte, Horsetooth Reservoir, and Masonville.
</abstract>
			<purpose>
Data used and/or developed by the Rocky Mountain National Park
GIS Program is used in the protection and management of
Rocky Mountain National Park.
</purpose>
			<langdata Sync="TRUE">en</langdata></descript>
		<timeperd>
			<timeinfo>
				<sngdate>
					<caldate>20050101</caldate>
				</sngdate>
			</timeinfo>
			<current>publication date</current>
		</timeperd>
		<status>
			<progress>Complete</progress>
			<update>As needed</update>
		</status>
		<spdom>
			<bounding>
				<westbc Sync="TRUE">-106.009539</westbc>
				<eastbc Sync="TRUE">-105.123875</eastbc>
				<northbc Sync="TRUE">40.754168</northbc>
				<southbc Sync="TRUE">39.996896</southbc>
			</bounding>
		</spdom>
		<keywords>
			<theme>
				<themekt>none</themekt>
				<themekey>Rocky Mountain National Park</themekey>
				<themekey>water</themekey>
				<themekey>hydrography</themekey>
				<themekey>river</themekey>
				<themekey>stream</themekey>
				<themekey>creek</themekey>
				<themekey>lake</themekey>
				<themekey>glacier</themekey>
				<themekey>reservoir</themekey>
				<themekey>marsh</themekey>
				<themekey>ditch</themekey>
				<themekey>canal</themekey>
			</theme>
			<place>
				<placekt>none</placekt>
				<placekey>Rocky Mountain National Park</placekey>
				<placekey>Colorado</placekey>
				<placekey>Larimer County</placekey>
				<placekey>Boulder County</placekey>
				<placekey>Grand County</placekey>
				<placekey>Estes Park</placekey>
				<placekey>Grand Lake</placekey>
			</place>
		</keywords>
		<accconst>None</accconst>
		<useconst>Not for use at scales greater than 1:24000</useconst>
		<ptcontac>
			<cntinfo>
				<cntperp>
					<cntper>GIS Coordinator</cntper>
					<cntorg>Rocky Mountain National Park GIS Program</cntorg>
				</cntperp>
				<cntpos>GIS Coordinator</cntpos>
				<cntaddr>
					<addrtype>mailing and physical address</addrtype>
					<address>US Hwy 36</address>
					<city>Estes Park</city>
					<state>Colorado</state>
					<postal>80517</postal>
					<country>USA</country>
				</cntaddr>
				<cntvoice>N/A</cntvoice>
				<cntfax>N/A</cntfax>
				<cntemail>romo_gis_coordinator@nps.gov</cntemail>
			</cntinfo>
		</ptcontac>
		<native Sync="TRUE">Microsoft Windows XP Version 5.1 (Build 2600) Service Pack 2; ESRI ArcCatalog 9.2.2.1350</native>
		<natvform Sync="TRUE">Shapefile</natvform></idinfo>
	<dataqual>
		<attracc>
			<attraccr>
The attribute accuracy is deductively estimated to be "good".
If a higher proof of data accuracy is required, do not use
these data. User is advised to FULLY and CAREFULLY READ the
"DISTRIBUTION LIABILITY" section of this metadata before using
this data.
</attraccr>
		</attracc>
		<logic>Polygon and chain-node topology present.</logic>
		<complete>
Data is considered complete. Some datasets are parkwide in scope,
while others were developed and/or updated to address specific
management concerns within particular spatial coordinates.  Users of
this data are advised to FULLY and CAREFULLY READ the "DISTRIBUTION
LIABILITY" section of this metadata before using this data.
</complete>
		<posacc>
			<horizpa>
				<horizpar>
Horizontal accuracy varies depending on the source of individual
components within the data.  Data derived from USGS data (DLGs, DEMs, DOQQs)
are assumed to meet National Map Accuracy standards, though extensive
experience in using USGS data for the Rocky Mountain National Park
area has shown that many data components have spatial errors exceeding
the National Map Accuracy standards. Data produced from GPS
(Global Positioning System) field data is assumed to be spatially
accurate to within 2-5 meters.
</horizpar>
			</horizpa>
		</posacc>
		<lineage>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>
The park acquired 17 1:24000-scale USGS DLG datafiles covering 17 7.5
minute quads of Rocky Mountain National Park.  This is the only 1:24000-scale
USGS DLG data available for this area (Aug 1998).  The USGS quads covered
by this DLG data are: Clark Peak, Chambers Lake, Comanche Peak, Pingree Park,
Mount Richthofen, Fall River Pass, Trail Ridge, Estes Park, Glen Haven,
Bowen Mountain, Grand Lake, McHenrys Peak, Panorama Peak, Trail
Mountain, Shadow Mountain, Isolation Peak, and Allens Park.  This data
was used as the primary basis for this coverage.

The data was received in DLG-3 optional format and was imported into the
data base using the ARC/INFO DLGARC command.  The line attributes in
the resulting "&lt;cover&gt;.ACODE" file were moved to the &lt;cover&gt;.AAT file
using the ARC/INFO command JOINITEM.  Similarly, the polygon attributes in
the "&lt;cover&gt;.PCODE" file were moved to the &lt;cover&gt;.PAT file
using the ARC/INFO command JOINITEM.

Cartographic Feature Files were used to fill in and extend this coverage
in and around Rocky Mountain National Park.  The 22 USGS 7.5 minute quads
covered by this CFF data are: Boulder, Gold Hill, Ward, Monarch Lake,
Strawberry Lake, Granby, Lyons, Raymond, Pinewood Lake, Longs Peak, Masonville,
Drake, Horsetooth Reservoir, Buckhorn Mountain, Crystal Mountain, Laporte,
Poudre Park, Big Narrows, Rustic, Kinikinik, Boston Peak, and Rawah Lakes.

"A Cartographic Feature File (CFF) is a digital data file containing a vector
representation of the point and line features shown on a Forest Service
Primary Base Series (PBS) map. CFF data are collected by digitizing PBS
maps and revised using correction guide information provided by field units.
The feature categories contained in the CFF are: transportation (roads and
trails), streams and water bodies, political and administrative boundaries,
land ownership, and other cultural features. Elevation contours, vegetation,
and text (geographic names, labels, etc.) are not included in the CFF."

The USFS CFF data was in ARC/INFO export format and was retrieved from the
Colorado Rockies Regional Cooperative (CORRC) server.  CORRC has since
ceased to exist.

The USFS CFF data was imported into 22 separate coverages using the ARC/INFO
command IMPORT.  These coverages were then combined into one coverage using
the ARC/INFO command APPEND.  No polygon attributes were present in the CFF
data.  Attributes were added to vectors and polygons using the ARC/INFO ARCEDIT
module and ARC/INFO TABLES commands.  Items of CFF origin in the &lt;cover&gt;.AAT
file were altered to match those created and added to the DLG derived coverage.
The DLG and CFF derived coverages were joined together using the ARC/INFO
command APPEND.

Additional vectors were added, and some 1:24000-scale vectors were
replaced with more accurate vectors created by collecting GPS data.
Line data were collected using Trimble GPS (Global Positioning
System) equipment. All data was post-processed with Trimble's software
resulting in an accuracy of 2-5 meters. Line features were edited and splined
to clean up vectors using the ARC/INFO ARCEDIT module.  Line features were
edited and snapped to create polygons using the ARC/INFO ARCEDIT
module.  Attributes were added to vectors and polygons using the ARC/INFO
ARCEDIT module and ARC/INFO TABLES commands, though some attributes were
attached to the data in the field using a pre-defined data dictionary.  See
&lt;URL:http://www.trimble.com&gt; for additional information regarding the
specifications of Trimble equipment.  Presently (July 1998) Rocky Mountain
National Park is using a Trimble Pathfinder Professional and Trimble
GeoExplorer IIs to collect GPS data.

Additionally, some vectors were added and others adjusted using heads-up
digitizing technique (digitizing off of the computer screen) using
1:12000-scale USGS DOQQs as a backdrop.

Additionally, some vectors were added and others adjusted using heads-up
digitizing technique using color DOQQ's developed from September 2001 aerial
photography as a backdrop.

Additionally, attributes were added to vectors and polygons using the
ARC/INFO ARCEDIT module and ARC/INFO TABLES commands, though some attributes
were attached to the data in the field using a pre-defined data dictionary
when GPS data was collected.  MAJOR and MINOR attributes were derived from the
text description supplied by the CFF item "CFF_WORD", and the final text
field DESCRIPTION was populated with the MINOR1 code description as defined in
the USGS "Digital Line Graphs From 1:24,000-Scale Maps--Data Users Guide 1".

Additionally, the NAME text field was populated with the official USGS place
name for each feature as identified on paper 1:24000-scale 7.5 minute USGS
quads.  The SOURCE item and SYMBOL item were also populated at this time.
</procdesc>
				<procdate>20050101</procdate>
			</procstep>
			<procstep><procdesc Sync="TRUE">Dataset copied.</procdesc><srcused Sync="TRUE"></srcused><date Sync="TRUE">20080903</date><time Sync="TRUE">14181200</time></procstep></lineage>
	</dataqual>
	<spdoinfo>
		<direct Sync="TRUE">Vector</direct>
		<ptvctinf>
			<sdtsterm Name="Lakes">
				<sdtstype Sync="TRUE">G-polygon</sdtstype>
				<ptvctcnt Sync="TRUE">0</ptvctcnt>
			</sdtsterm>
			<sdtsterm>
				<sdtstype>String</sdtstype>
				<ptvctcnt>12601</ptvctcnt>
			</sdtsterm>
			<sdtsterm>
				<sdtstype>GT-polygon composed of chains</sdtstype>
				<ptvctcnt>2682</ptvctcnt>
			</sdtsterm>
			<esriterm Name="Lakes"><efeatyp Sync="TRUE">Simple</efeatyp><efeageom Sync="TRUE">Polygon</efeageom><esritopo Sync="TRUE">FALSE</esritopo><efeacnt Sync="TRUE">0</efeacnt><spindex Sync="TRUE">FALSE</spindex><linrefer Sync="TRUE">FALSE</linrefer></esriterm></ptvctinf>
	</spdoinfo>
	<spref>
		<horizsys>
			<planar>
				<planci>
					<plance Sync="TRUE">coordinate pair</plance>
					<coordrep>
						<absres Sync="TRUE">0.000000</absres>
						<ordres Sync="TRUE">0.000000</ordres>
					</coordrep>
					<plandu Sync="TRUE">meters</plandu>
				</planci>
				<gridsys><gridsysn Sync="TRUE">Universal Transverse Mercator</gridsysn><utm><utmzone Sync="TRUE">13</utmzone><transmer><sfctrmer Sync="TRUE">0.999600</sfctrmer><longcm Sync="TRUE">-105.000000</longcm><latprjo Sync="TRUE">0.000000</latprjo><feast Sync="TRUE">500000.000000</feast><fnorth Sync="TRUE">0.000000</fnorth></transmer></utm></gridsys></planar>
			<geodetic>
				<horizdn Sync="TRUE">North American Datum of 1983</horizdn>
				<ellips Sync="TRUE">Geodetic Reference System 80</ellips>
				<semiaxis Sync="TRUE">6378137.000000</semiaxis>
				<denflat Sync="TRUE">298.257222</denflat>
			</geodetic>
			<cordsysn><geogcsn Sync="TRUE">GCS_North_American_1983</geogcsn><projcsn Sync="TRUE">NAD_1983_UTM_Zone_13N</projcsn></cordsysn></horizsys>
	</spref>
	<eainfo>
		<overview>
			<eaover>
If this dataset if a COVERAGE: the first four items in the polygon attribute table (PAT), or the first seven items in the arc attribute table (AAT) are automatically generated by ARC/INFO software.  Contact ESRI (Environmental Systems Research Institute, Inc.) or read their literature for detailed descriptions of their internal file structure.  ESRI can be reached at &lt;URL:http://www.esri.com.&gt;

If this dataset is a SHAPEFILE, the first two items in the data table are automatically generated.   Contact ESRI or read their literature for detailed descriptions of their internal file structure.  ESRI can be reached at &lt;URL:http://www.esri.com.&gt;

These attributes are common for both the VECTOR and  POLYGON data:

The MAJ0R1 item is the USGS DLG major1 attribute code.

The MINOR1 item is the USGS DLG minor1 attribute code.

The MAJ0R2 item is the USGS DLG major2 attribute code.

The MINOR2 item is the USGS DLG minor2 attribute code.

For more information and examples of attribute codes, see the following USGS publication:
"Digital Line Graphs From 1:24,000-Scale Maps--Data Users Guide 1".

The SYMBOL item is populated by a number that represents either a polygon fill or a line symbol.  Used exclusively in cartographic production in ArcInfo ArcPlot.

The DESCRIPTION item is a text field that describes the feature in plain text.  Descriptions can be a single word or a simple phrase.

The NAME item is a text field populated by the official USGS place name of the feature.

The SOURCE item defines the source of individual components within the data set.  Values may include:

&gt; DOQQ/USGS - arcs, polygons, and/or points derived from features visible on
&gt; 1:12000 USGS digital orthophotoquads
&gt; DOQQ/2001 - arcs, polygons, and/or points derived from features visible on
&gt; ROMO's color digital orthophotoquads
&gt; 1:24K DLG - components originally from 1:24000 USGS digital line graph
&gt;data
&gt; GPS - arcs, polygons, and/or points collected with Global Positioning
&gt; System equipment

Other values might exist.

The NOTE item contains any additional pertinent information in text format.  Additional information can be a single word or a simple phrase.

The FISH item is a alphanumeric code that relates to a fish inventory database compiled by the USFWS for RMNP.  Those data are not included with this dataset.

This attribute only applies to the POLYGON data:

The ACRES item is a numeric field populated by multiplying the AREA item by 0.0002471054, or by use of the NPS AlaskaPak for ArcGIS extension.

This attribute only applies to the VECTOR data:

The MILES item is populated by multiplying the LENGTH item by 3.280839895, or by use of the NPS AlaskaPak for ArcGIS extension.
</eaover>
			<eadetcit>none</eadetcit>
		</overview>
		<detailed Name="Lakes"><enttyp><enttypl Sync="TRUE">Lakes</enttypl><enttypt Sync="TRUE">Feature Class</enttypt><enttypc Sync="TRUE">0</enttypc></enttyp><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">FID</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">FID</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">OID</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">4</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale><attrdef Sync="TRUE">Internal feature number.</attrdef><attrdefs Sync="TRUE">ESRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom Sync="TRUE">Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">Shape</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">Shape</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Geometry</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">0</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale><attrdef Sync="TRUE">Feature geometry.</attrdef><attrdefs Sync="TRUE">ESRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom Sync="TRUE">Coordinates defining the features.</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">MAJOR1</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">MAJOR1</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Number</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">6</attwidth></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">MINOR1</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">MINOR1</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Number</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">6</attwidth></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">MAJOR2</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">MAJOR2</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Number</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">6</attwidth></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">MINOR2</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">MINOR2</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Number</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">6</attwidth></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">SYMBOL</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">SYMBOL</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Number</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">3</attwidth></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">DESCRIPTIO</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">DESCRIPTIO</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">30</attwidth></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">NAME</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">NAME</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">30</attwidth></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">SOURCE</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">SOURCE</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">30</attwidth></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">ACRES</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">ACRES</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Number</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">8</attwidth><atnumdec Sync="TRUE">1</atnumdec></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">NOTE</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">NOTE</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">30</attwidth></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">FISH</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">FISH</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">12</attwidth></attr></detailed></eainfo>
	<distinfo>
		<distrib>
			<cntinfo>
				<cntperp>
					<cntper>GIS Coordinator</cntper>
					<cntorg>Rocky Mountain National Park GIS Program</cntorg>
				</cntperp>
				<cntaddr>
					<addrtype>mailing and physical address</addrtype>
					<address>US Hwy 36</address>
					<city>Estes Park</city>
					<state>CO</state>
					<postal>80517</postal>
					<country>USA</country>
				</cntaddr>
				<cntvoice>N/A</cntvoice>
				<cntfax>N/A</cntfax>
				<cntemail>romo_gis_coordinator@nps.gov</cntemail>
				<cntinst>Contact via email ONLY.</cntinst>
			</cntinfo>
		</distrib>
		<distliab>
The National Park Service shall not be held liable for improper or incorrect use of the data described and/or contained herein. These data and related graphics (if available) are not legal documents and are not intended to be used as such. The information contained in these data is dynamic and may change over time. The data are not better than the original sources from which they were derived. It is the responsibility of the data user to use the data appropriately and consistant within the limitations of geospatial data in general and these data in particular. Any related graphics (if available) are intended to aid the data user in acquiring relevant data; it is not appropriate to use related graphics as data. 

The National Park Service gives no warranty, expressed or implied, as to the accuracy, reliability, or completeness of these data. It is strongly recommended that these data are directly acquired from an NPS server and not indirectly through other sources which may have changed the data in some way. Although these data have been processed successfully on a computer system at the National Park Service, no warranty expressed or implied is made regarding the utility of the data on another system or for general or scientific purposes, nor shall the act of distribution constitute any such warranty. This disclaimer applies both to individual use of the data and aggregate use with other data.
</distliab>
		<stdorder>
			<digform>
				<digtinfo>
					<formname>Varies: Shapefiles with associated DBF lookup tables, or personal geodatabase</formname>
					<formverd>20060720</formverd>
					<filedec>no compression applied</filedec>
					<transize Sync="TRUE">0.000</transize><dssize Sync="TRUE">0.000</dssize></digtinfo>
				<digtopt>
					<offoptn>
						<offmedia>CD-ROM</offmedia>
						<reccap>
							<recden>650</recden>
							<recdenu>MB</recdenu>
						</reccap>
						<recfmt>ISO 9660</recfmt>
					</offoptn>
				</digtopt>
			</digform>
			<fees>None</fees>
			<ordering>
Contact via email ONLY.  
The RMNP GIS Program does ask to receive blank CD-R media in return for those sent out.
</ordering>
		</stdorder>
		<resdesc Sync="TRUE">Downloadable Data</resdesc></distinfo>
	<metainfo>
		<metd Sync="TRUE">20080626</metd>
		<metrd>20050101</metrd>
		<metc>
			<cntinfo>
				<cntorgp>
					<cntorg>Rocky Mountain National Park GIS Program</cntorg>
					<cntper>GIS Coordinator</cntper>
				</cntorgp>
				<cntpos>GIS Coordinator</cntpos>
				<cntaddr>
					<addrtype>mailing and physical address</addrtype>
					<address>US Hwy 36</address>
					<city>Estes Park</city>
					<state>Colorado</state>
					<postal>80517</postal>
					<country>USA</country>
				</cntaddr>
				<cntvoice>N/A</cntvoice>
				<cntfax>N/A</cntfax>
				<cntemail>romo_gis_coordinator@nps.gov</cntemail>
			</cntinfo>
		</metc>
		<metstdn Sync="TRUE">FGDC Content Standards for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
		<metstdv Sync="TRUE">FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
		<mettc Sync="TRUE">local time</mettc>
		<langmeta Sync="TRUE">en</langmeta><metextns><onlink Sync="TRUE">http://www.esri.com/metadata/esriprof80.html</onlink><metprof Sync="TRUE">ESRI Metadata Profile</metprof></metextns></metainfo>
	<dataIdInfo><envirDesc Sync="TRUE">Microsoft Windows XP Version 5.1 (Build 2600) Service Pack 2; ESRI ArcCatalog 9.2.2.1350</envirDesc><dataLang><languageCode Sync="TRUE" value="en"></languageCode></dataLang><idCitation><resTitle Sync="TRUE">Lakes</resTitle><presForm><PresFormCd Sync="TRUE" value="005"></PresFormCd></presForm></idCitation><spatRpType><SpatRepTypCd Sync="TRUE" value="001"></SpatRepTypCd></spatRpType></dataIdInfo><mdLang><languageCode Sync="TRUE" value="en"></languageCode></mdLang><mdStanName Sync="TRUE">ISO 19115 Geographic Information - Metadata</mdStanName><mdStanVer Sync="TRUE">DIS_ESRI1.0</mdStanVer><mdChar><CharSetCd Sync="TRUE" value="004"></CharSetCd></mdChar><mdHrLv><ScopeCd Sync="TRUE" value="005"></ScopeCd></mdHrLv><mdHrLvName Sync="TRUE">dataset</mdHrLvName><distInfo><distributor><distorTran><onLineSrc><orDesc Sync="TRUE">002</orDesc><linkage Sync="TRUE">file://</linkage><protocol Sync="TRUE">Local Area Network</protocol></onLineSrc><transSize Sync="TRUE">0.000</transSize></distorTran><distorFormat><formatName Sync="TRUE">Shapefile</formatName></distorFormat></distributor></distInfo><refSysInfo><RefSystem><refSysID><identCode Sync="TRUE">NAD_1983_UTM_Zone_13N</identCode></refSysID></RefSystem></refSysInfo><spatRepInfo><VectSpatRep><topLvl><TopoLevCd Sync="TRUE" value="001"></TopoLevCd></topLvl><geometObjs Name="Lakes"><geoObjTyp><GeoObjTypCd Sync="TRUE" value="001"></GeoObjTypCd></geoObjTyp><geoObjCnt Sync="TRUE">0</geoObjCnt></geometObjs></VectSpatRep></spatRepInfo><Esri><SyncDate>20080626</SyncDate><SyncTime>12525200</SyncTime><ModDate>20080626</ModDate><ModTime>12525200</ModTime><DataProperties><lineage><Process Name="Clip_3" ToolSource="C:\Program Files\ArcGIS\ArcToolbox\Toolboxes\Analysis Tools.tbx\Clip" Date="20080626" Time="125254">Clip "C:\Documents and Settings\benwhite\Desktop\RMNP\Water_Bodies\lakes.shp" "C:\Documents and Settings\benwhite\Desktop\RMNP\Boundaries\bndry2006.shp" "C:\Documents and Settings\benwhite\Desktop\RMNP\Clips\Lakes.shp" #</Process><Process Name="Project_4" ToolSource="C:\Program Files\ArcGIS\ArcToolbox\Toolboxes\Data Management Tools.tbx\Project" Date="20080903" Time="141813">Project "C:\Documents and Settings\benwhite\Desktop\lab2\Lakes.shp" "C:\Documents and Settings\benwhite\Desktop\lab2\Lakes_Project.shp" PROJCS['WGS_1984_UTM_Zone_13N',GEOGCS['GCS_WGS_1984',DATUM['D_WGS_1984',SPHEROID['WGS_1984',6378137.0,298.257223563]],PRIMEM['Greenwich',0.0],UNIT['Degree',0.0174532925199433]],PROJECTION['Transverse_Mercator'],PARAMETER['False_Easting',500000.0],PARAMETER['False_Northing',0.0],PARAMETER['Central_Meridian',-105.0],PARAMETER['Scale_Factor',0.9996],PARAMETER['Latitude_Of_Origin',0.0],UNIT['Meter',1.0]] NAD_1983_To_WGS_1984_1 PROJCS['NAD_1983_UTM_Zone_13N',GEOGCS['GCS_North_American_1983',DATUM['D_North_American_1983',SPHEROID['GRS_1980',6378137.0,298.257222101]],PRIMEM['Greenwich',0.0],UNIT['Degree',0.0174532925199433]],PROJECTION['Transverse_Mercator'],PARAMETER['False_Easting',500000.0],PARAMETER['False_Northing',0.0],PARAMETER['Central_Meridian',-105.0],PARAMETER['Scale_Factor',0.9996],PARAMETER['Latitude_Of_Origin',0.0],UNIT['Meter',1.0]]</Process></lineage><itemProps><itemLocation><linkage Sync="TRUE">file://\\DESKTOP-HKNFILC\C$\Users\MapGirl\Documents\NR 322 files\2018 Spring semester\Labs\Lab 2 Explore Spatial Data\Data\Lakes</linkage><protocol Sync="TRUE">Local Area Network</protocol></itemLocation></itemProps><copyHistory><copy source="C:\Users\MapGirl\Documents\NR 322 files\2018 Spring semester\Labs\Lab 2 Explore Spatial Data\Data\lab2\Lakes" dest="\\DESKTOP-HKNFILC\C$\Users\MapGirl\Documents\NR 322 files\2018 Spring semester\Labs\Lab 2 Explore Spatial Data\Data\Lakes" date="20180123" time="20370600"></copy></copyHistory></DataProperties><MetaID>{896DEF71-DD31-4A1A-A2ED-A924121000D7}</MetaID><CreaDate>20080903</CreaDate><CreaTime>14181200</CreaTime><SyncOnce>TRUE</SyncOnce></Esri><mdDateSt Sync="TRUE">20080626</mdDateSt></metadata>
